&gt；&gt；steve kinney：猜猜现在轮到谁了，它是你的。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Guess who's
turn it is now, it's yours.
因此我们知道NoteView，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：NoteView是
So we know the NoteView,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: NoteView is
使用这个降价组件。
using this Markdown component.
我们知道Markdown组件现在占用了28千字节。
We know that the Markdown component
right now is taking up 28 kilobytes.
我有一些关于角色实体的消息要告诉你，他们在一起[笑]对吗？
I've got some news for you about character
entities, they're together [LAUGH] right?
这是另一个25，所以这是另一个最初的10%，对吗？
Which is another 25, so
that's another initial 10%, right?
或者目前是我们最终捆绑包的20%
Or it's currently at this point
20% of our resulting bundle
我们现在不需要的东西。
that we don't need immediately.
所以如果我们能使用同样的技术那就太好了，
So it would be great if we
could use the same technique,
创建可加载的NoteView。
create a loadable NoteView.
然后转到NoteView容器并将NoteView替换为可加载的NoteView。
Then go to the NoteView container and swap
out NoteView for the loadable NoteView.
然后我们一起回来，我们可以重新分析它。
And then we'll come back together and
we'll be able to reanalyze it.
我要在这上面做一个分支叫做实时编码。
I'm gonna make a branch on
this called live coding.
我要把我现在拥有的东西推出来，这样你就可以把它拉下来了。
I'm gonna push out what I have
right now so you can pull it down.
如果你不喜欢纱线安装或MPM安装，你可以有那些依赖。
If you didn't like yarn install or mpm
install, you can have those dependencies.
你可以带着它转一圈，看看它会怎么样，然后
You can take it for a spin and
see how it goes, and
那我们大约20分钟后一起做
then we'll do it together
in about 20 minutes.